Save the Pine Bush, Inc.; Records apap125
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Lawsuits and Challenges, 1977-2000; 5; 7.03 cubic ft. and 2 oversize folders
  - Lawsuits, 1977-2000; 5.1
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Madison Avenue Office Park, Counterclaim, 1985 (Box 4 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Madison Avenue Office Park, Brief of Appellant Willard T. Andersen, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Madison Avenue Office Park, Brief on Behalf of Plaintiff-Petitioner-Respondents, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Madison Avenue Office Park, Brief of New York State Builders Association, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Madison Avenue Office Park, Responsive Brief on Behalf of Plaintiff-Petitioner-Respondents, 1987 (Box 4 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, The Woodlands at Pine Ridge, Notice of Petition, 1986 (Box 4 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1-3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Memoranda, 1986 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Various Litigation Papers, 1986-1989 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Final Regulatory and Revised Regulatory Impact Statement, 1987 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Comments of Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1988 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Press Releases, 1988-1990 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Petition for Party Status, 1988 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 9)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Affidavit and Memorandum, 1989 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 10)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Interrogatories, 1989 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 11)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Notice of Motion, 1989 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 12)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Amicus Testimony of John Cryan, 1989 (Box 5 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 13-14)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Pre-filed Testimony Paul Opler, 1989 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Pre-filed Testimony Don Rittner, Undated (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Pre-filed Testimony John Shuey, 1989 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Memo to Parties, Rulings, 1989 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Briefs, 1989 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Permit to Construct, 1990 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Decision, 1990 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Supreme Court Litigation, 1990 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Affidavit, 1991 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 9)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Affidavit, 1991 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 10)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Verified Answer, 1991 (Box 6 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 11)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Notice of Petition, 1992 (Box 7 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1-2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Affidavit, 1992 (Box 7 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Verified Answers and Affidavits, 1992 (Box 7 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Reply Affidavit, 1992 (Box 7 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Freedom of Information Act Request, 1993 (Box 7 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Freedom of Information Act Papers, 1993 (Box 7 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Appeal, 1993; 2 copies (Box 7 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8-9)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 7 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 10)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, SEFCU, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 8 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, SEFCU, Affidavits, 1987 (Box 8 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, SEFCU, Notice of Motion/Notice of Appeal, 1987 (Box 8 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, SEFCU, Memo of Law/Brief, 1987 (Box 8 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Annexation, 1988 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Full Environmental Assessment Form, 1990 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Evictions, Water Issues, 1990-1991 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Albany City Record Resolutions, 1994-1995 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Press Releases and News Clippings, 1995-1998 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Local Laws, 1970-1998 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Albany Pine Bush Commission Correspondence, 1998 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Affidavits, 1998 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 9)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Preliminary Injunction, 1998 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 10)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Notice of Entry, 1998 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 11)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Donald Zee Correspondence, 1998 (Box 9 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 12)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Donald Crospy Correspondence, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Planning Board Memoranda and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Notice of Complete Application, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Planning Board Minutes and Agendas, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Plaintiff Lists, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Declaration of Deeds, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Notice of Petition, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Lynne Jackson's Correspondence and Drafts, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Freedom of Information Act Request, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 9)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Notice of Cross Motion, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 10)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Lewis Oliver Letter, 1998 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 11)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Harmon Homes, 1999 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 12)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Harmon Homes, 1999 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 13)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Reply Brief, 2000 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 14)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Memorandum and Order, 2000 (Box 10 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 15)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, 40 Karner Rd. and 300 Washington Ave. Extension, Reply Affidavit, 1991 (Box 11 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, 40 Karner Rd. and 300 Washington Ave. Extension, Reply Memorandum of Law, Undated (Box 11 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany - 40 Karner Rd. and 300 Washington Ave. Extension, Affidavit, 1992 (Box 11 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Pine East Office Rd. 300 Washington Ave. Extension, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1994 (Box 11 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4-5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany Karner Pines, Brief on Behalf of Appellant, 1992; 2 copies (Box 11 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6-7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Karner Pines, Brief and Appendix, 1992 (Box 11 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Karner Pines, Brief on Behalf of Respondents, 1992; 2 copies (Box 11 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 9-10)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Loop Road, Freedom of Information Act Papers, Notes, Maps, 1992-1993 (Box 12 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Loop Road, Freedom of Information Act Papers, 1993-1994 (Box 12 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Loop Road, Notice of Petition, 1994 (Box 12 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Loop Road, Decision and Order, 1994 (Box 12 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1993 (Box 13 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1-4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Correspondence, Notes, Board Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 14 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Order to Show Cause, 1994; 2 copies (Box 4 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2-3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Memorandum of Law/Intervener's Supplement to Memorandum of Law, 1994 (Box 14 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Memorandum of Law, 1994; copy 2 (Box 14 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Brief in Behalf of Petitioner-Appellant, 1995; 2 copies (Box 14 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6-7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Albany Pine Bush Preserve Commission, Notice of Petition, 1993 (Box 15 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Notice of Petition/Verified Petition, 1993 (Box 16 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Memorandum of Law on Behalf of Petitioners, 1993 (Box 16 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Notice of Motion to Dismiss Petition, 1993 (Box 16 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Memorandum of Law/Dismissal of Petition, 1993 (Box 16 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Intervener Reply to Memo of Law, 1993 (Box 16 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Memorandum of Law in Behalf of Petitioners-Appellants, 1994; 2 copies (Box 16 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6-7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Record on Appeal Vol. 1, 1994 (Box 17 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1-3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Record on Appeal Vol. 2, 1994 (Box 17 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4-6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Pine Haven Estates, Record on Appeal Vol. 4, 1994 (Box 17 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7-8)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Karner Dunes Adventure Park, Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1994 (Box 18 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Karner Dunes Adventure Park, Freedom of Information Act Material, 1994 (Box 18 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Karner Dunes Adventure Park, Notice of Petition, 1994 (Box 18 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Karner Dunes Adventure Park, Notice of Petition, 1994; 2 copies (Box 19 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1-6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Landfill Expansion, Undated (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court, Seven Maps, 1991 (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court 1779 (photocopy), Undated (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court Grading Plan, 1990; 2 copies (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court Plan, 1990; 3 copies (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. Town of Guilderland, Willow Street/Tera Court Utility Plan, 1990; 2 copies (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, 40 Karner Rd. and 300 Washington Ave Extension, 1992 (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Map 1 of DEIS, 1993 (Box 23 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Map 2 of DEIS, 1993; 2 copies (Box 23 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2-3)
    - Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Map 5 of DEIS, 1993 (Box 23 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
  - Challenges, 1984-1998; 5.2
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Energy Law, 1984 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Articles, 1990-1995 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Robert Abrams Paper, 1997 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Development Plans and Zoning Application, 1997 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Non-Save the Pine Bush Correspondence, 1997 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Miscellaneous Notes and Papers, 1997 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Town of Colonie Board Meeting Agendas, 1997 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1997 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8-10)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1997 (Box 20 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 11-12)
    - Pine Valley Development, 1986 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 1)
    - ANSWERS Watershed Waste Authority, 1992 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 2)
    - Spawn Road Subdivision, 1992 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 3)
    - Guilderland American Legion Post Building, 1994 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 4)
    - New Hope Gospel Fellowship, 1994 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - Rose Garden Subdivision, 1994 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - Guilderland YMCA Development Project, 1996-1997 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Guilderland YMCA Development Project, Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 1997 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8)
    - Colonie Developments, 1997 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 9)
    - Morris Road Park, 1997 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 10)
    - Guilderland Water Interconnect, 1998 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 11)
    - Fenney Subdivision, 1998 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 12)
    - Guilderland Comprehensive Plan, 1998-2000 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 13)
    - Northeast Welders Supply Limited, 1999 (Box 21 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 14)
    - Spawn Road Subdivision, 1992 (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Maps, 1997 (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 9)
    - Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Final Environmental Impact Statement, Maps, 1997 (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 10)
    - Feeney Subdivision Proposal, 1998 (Box 22 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 11)
    - New Hope Gospel Fellowship, 1994 (Box 23 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 5)
    - New Hope Gospel Fellowship, 1994 (Box 23 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 6)
    - New Hope Gospel Fellowship, 1994 (Box 23 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 7)
    - Morris Road Park, 1997 (Box 23 (5-Lawsuits and Challenges), Folder 8)
    - 1. Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Map 3 of DEIS, 1993 (Oversized 1)
    - 2. Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Map 4 of DEIS, 1993 (Oversized 1)
    - 3. Save the Pine Bush vs. City of Albany, Columbia Circle, Map 4 of DEIS, 1993 (Oversized 1)
    - 4. New Hope Gospel Fellowship, 1994 (Oversized 1)
    - 5. New Hope Gospel Fellowship, 1994 (Oversized 1)
    - 6. New Hope Gospel Fellowship, 1994 (Oversized 1)
    - 7. Morris Road Park, 1997 (Oversized 1)
    - 1. Rose Garden Subdivision, Concept Plan, 1992 (Oversized 2)
    - 2. Guilderland YMCA Development Project, Site Plan, 1997 (Oversized 2)
    - 3-4. Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Concept Plan, 1997; 2 copies (Oversized 2)
    - 5-6. Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Preliminary Floor Plan, 1997; 2 copies (Oversized 2)
    - 7-8. Golden Bear Family Golf Center, Site Analysis Plan, 1997; 2 copies (Oversized 2)
    - 9-10. Fenney Subdivision, Concept Plan, 1998; 2 copies (Oversized 2)
    - 11-12. Northeast Welders Supply Limited, Site Analysis Plan, 1999; 2 copies (Oversized 2)
    - 13. Northeast Welders Supply Limited, Main Building Concept Floor Plan, 1999 (Oversized 2)
    - 14. Northeast Welders Supply Limited, Flammable Storage and Coverage Storage Buildings Covered Floor Plans, 1999 (Oversized 2)